<resources>
    <string name="app_name">10 Days of One Piece</string>
    <string name="title">10 DAYS OF</string>
    <string name="day1">DAY 1</string>
    <string name="mugiwara1">MONKEY D. LUFFY</string>
    <string name="alias1">Straw Hat</string>
    <string name="description1">The founder and captain of the increasingly infamous and powerful Straw Hat Pirates, as well as the most powerful of its top fighters. He desires to find the legendary treasure left behind by the late Gol D. Roger and thereby become the Pirate King.</string>
    <string name="day2">DAY 2</string>
    <string name="mugiwara2">RORONOA ZORO</string>
    <string name="alias2">The Pirate Hunter</string>
    <string name="description2">He is a main combatant of the Straw Hat Pirates, one of their two swordsmen, one of the Senior Officers of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet, and is publicly recognized as the right-hand man of his crew\'s captain Monkey D. Luffy. Formerly a bounty hunter, he is the second member of Luffy\'s crew and the first to join it. His dream is to become the greatest swordsman in the world, in order to honor a promise he made to his deceased childhood friend and distant cousin Kuina.</string>
    <string name="day3">DAY 3</string>
    <string name="mugiwara3">NAMI</string>
    <string name="alias3">The Cat Burglar</string>
    <string name="description3">She is the navigator of the Straw Hat Pirates and one of the Senior Officers of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet. She is the third member of the crew and the second to join it. Her dream is to make a map of the entire world.</string>
    <string name="day4">DAY 4</string>
    <string name="mugiwara4">GOD USOPP</string>
    <string name="alias4">Sogeking</string>
    <string name="description4">He is the sniper of the Straw Hat Pirates and one of the Senior Officers of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet. He is the fourth member of the crew and the third to join it. Despite his usual cowardice, Usopp dreams of becoming a brave warrior of the sea just like his father and lives every day in pursuit of living up to this dream.</string>
    <string name="day5">DAY 5</string>
    <string name="mugiwara5">VINSMOKE SANJI</string>
    <string name="alias5">Black Leg</string>
    <string name="description5">He is the cook of the Straw Hat Pirates and one of the Senior Officers of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet. He is the fifth member of the crew and the fourth to join it. His dream is to find the rumored chef\'s paradise, All Blue, which is where the East Blue, West Blue, North Blue, and South Blue meet, along with their wildlife.</string>
    <string name="day6">DAY 6</string>
    <string name="mugiwara6">TONY TONY CHOPPER</string>
    <string name="alias6">The Cotton Candy Lover</string>
    <string name="description6">He is the doctor of the Straw Hat Pirates and one of the Senior Officers of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet. He is the sixth member of the crew and the fifth to join it. Chopper is a reindeer that ate the Hito Hito no Mi, a Devil Fruit that allows its user to transform into a human hybrid at will.</string>
    <string name="day7">DAY 7</string>
    <string name="mugiwara7">NICO ROBIN</string>
    <string name="alias7">The Devil Child</string>
    <string name="description7">She is the archaeologist of the Straw Hat Pirates and one of the Senior Officers of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet. She is the seventh member of the crew and the sixth to join it. Robin ate the Hana Hana no Mi at a young age, giving her the power to reproduce her body parts (or her entire body) on any surface at will.</string>
    <string name="day8">DAY 8</string>
    <string name="mugiwara8">FRANKY</string>
    <string name="alias8">The Cyborg - Iron Man</string>
    <string name="description8">is the shipwright of the Straw Hat Pirates and one of the Senior Officers of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet. He is the crew\'s eighth member and the seventh to join it. He came to be a member of Tom\'s Workers, until an incident resulted in his body being heavily damaged and requiring him to augment himself into a cyborg.</string>
    <string name="day9">DAY 9</string>
    <string name="mugiwara9">BROOK</string>
    <string name="alias9">The Soul-King</string>
    <string name="description9">He is the musician of the Straw Hat Pirates, one of their two swordsmen, and one of the Senior Officers of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet. He is the ninth member of the crew and the eighth to join it. Brook ate the Yomi Yomi no Mi, which allowed him to return to life after death once. Brook eventually learned to tap deeper into the powers of his Devil Fruit, giving him significant control over his own soul and the souls of others.</string>
    <string name="day10">DAY 10</string>
    <string name="mugiwara10">JIMBEI</string>
    <string name="alias10">The Knight of the Sea</string>
    <string name="description10">He is the helmsman of the Straw Hat Pirates and one of the Senior Officers of the Straw Hat Grand Fleet. He is the tenth member of the crew and the ninth to join. Jinbe is a whale shark fish-man and a powerful master of Fish-Man Karate. His dream is to fulfill his former captain Fisher Tiger\'s dying wish of coexistence and equality between humans and fish-men.</string>
</resources>